<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Guides on ActiveState Platform Documentation</title>
    <link>//activestate.github.io/documentation-public/contributions/guides/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Guides on ActiveState Platform Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//activestate.github.io/documentation-public/contributions/guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started Guide</title>
      <link>//activestate.github.io/documentation-public/contributions/guides/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//activestate.github.io/documentation-public/contributions/guides/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>You can use the ActiveState Platform API to define repeatable, composable, serverless builds.
Tutorial Step-by step instruction on how to start a project. The tutorial is written for developers without GraphQL experience.
The tutorial covers:
 Authentication Connecting to the GraphQL endpoint Your first query Understanding mutations Exploring the capabilities of the API  Quick Start A one page summary of how to start a new project.
Where do I go next?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contents - Outline TOC</title>
      <link>//activestate.github.io/documentation-public/contributions/guides/toc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//activestate.github.io/documentation-public/contributions/guides/toc/</guid>
      <description>GraphQL &amp;amp; ActiveState Platform   &amp;ldquo;GraphQL allows you to declaratively express your data needs&amp;hellip;queries are the representation of the data you need.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Notice how the query signature exactly matches the returned JSON signature. This is possible because in GraphQL, you query against a schema that is the representation of your available data.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;GraphiQL is a UI that lets you 1) run queries against your data in the browser, and 2) dig into the structure of data available to you through a data type explorer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Builder Fundamentals Guide</title>
      <link>//activestate.github.io/documentation-public/contributions/guides/builder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//activestate.github.io/documentation-public/contributions/guides/builder/</guid>
      <description>What is the ActiveState Platform Builder? ActiveState Platform architecture diagram Package Database (aka Ingredients) Dependancy Resolver (aka Head Chef) Build Wrapper Design methodology Structure Example Supported build images Reference: Image Strawman
CircleCI provides quite detailed inforamtion about the configurations they support that your build will run on.
Executors and Images
Pre-Build CircleCI Docker Images
Artifacts References:
 Artifact Cache Key Components Artifacts Requirements Gathering  Best Practices Troubleshooting </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>