<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quick Start Guides on ActiveState Platform Documentation</title>
    <link>https://activestate.github.io/documentation-public/start/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Quick Start Guides on ActiveState Platform Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://activestate.github.io/documentation-public/start/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Platform Quick Start</title>
      <link>https://activestate.github.io/documentation-public/start/platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 17:26:16 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://activestate.github.io/documentation-public/start/platform/</guid>
      <description>Joining your first Organization When a colleague or ActiveState employee invites you to join the ActiveState Platform you will receive an email invitation to join a specific organization. You need to create your account for the ActiveState Platform and confirm that you want to join the organization.
 Open the email invite you received from notifications@activestate.com to join the organization. Click the link in the email, or copy and paste the link text into your browser address bar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State Tool CLI</title>
      <link>https://activestate.github.io/documentation-public/start/state-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://activestate.github.io/documentation-public/start/state-tool/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The State Tool is the command line interface for the ActiveState Platform. This quick start is for intermediate or advanced developers who want to get up and running right away.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ActiveState managed projects</title>
      <link>https://activestate.github.io/documentation-public/start/managed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://activestate.github.io/documentation-public/start/managed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Managed projects provide access to the ActiveState language distributions that are available to your organization. ActiveState manages and updates these language distributions, and packages them as installers you can download and install on your computer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom language runtimes</title>
      <link>https://activestate.github.io/documentation-public/start/build/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://activestate.github.io/documentation-public/start/build/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You can build a custom language runtime with the language, packages, and platforms you need.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security and Compliance</title>
      <link>https://activestate.github.io/documentation-public/start/security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://activestate.github.io/documentation-public/start/security/</guid>
      <description>Security &amp;amp; Compliance enables you to automatically identify out-of-date or unsecure Python packages running in your environment. To begin, you need to complete a few configuration steps to specify the applications to scan and how to organize the scan results in the Platform.
Note: The Security &amp;amp; Compliance tab provides access to the security features of the Platform. It is available for Organizations on the Business and Enterprise tiers.
Configuring Security &amp;amp; Compliance Security &amp;amp; Compliance requires configuration to map the ActivePython interpreter you want to scan for vulnerabilities with the identity in the ActiveState Platform where you want to record the packages scanned and any details for any vulnerabilities identified.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>